Today's video is about some really interesting and cool catsuits or this one for example
They're from Devil Walking and I think they're really cool for festivals and they also have like rave and party outfits
So let's go
All right first outfit and it's already a banger because I have abs now
How cool is that?
And boobs
If you like honest traders like I do you know why I said it like I said it. Anyway, I
think this is such a great design. My
goth heart is leaping with joy because it is
it's simply so nice and dark and I have like a
nice spot because how cool is that shading here?
Nice.
Maybe just take a second to see all the glory because the important part here is the shading. The white lines that make this really pop and give you like a kind of figure, give you structure and I think in club at night with less light it will look great as well.
Of course not only for goth clubs but for techno parties, raves, anywhere basically.
For some outfits there is a matching balaclava. This one is the matching for this catsuit.
And of course you can wear it if you're a motorcycle driver.
But I think if you're going to Burning Man and there's a lot of dust then this might come in handy to protect your face and your hair.
If you check out the description text you will find a discount code. I have some special prize for you for Devolv walking. I'm going to show you more outfits in the rest of the video but yeah I think this is already highlight.
another front set catsuit and this time completely different because this is neon pink it screams
color and pattern it's also available in green and there is a special black light design so if
you see the suit under black light it looks really really awesome this is only blue light and not
black light but you can already tell that the effect with a black light is going to be really
really cool if this is already look nice I already took some pictures with it too
and posted them on my youtube community tab you can also check that out and
everyone was like wow that is a crazy pattern and I said well it is printed it
is not textured but it is this kind of firm thick spandex and design is simply
printed on and it's a really really nice quality and of course also looks awesome
especially if you have a nice lighting one more time full body picture paired
it with some fun white heels or boots no sorry these are witches and they're the
most comfortable shoes for festival ever and now I'm going to change into this
one the special sauce here is obviously the cut out in the front of this
catsuit but I think the overall design is also really really nice this kind of
feather look feel like a bird paradise because it looks really really nice and
also like a bit trippy a bit psychedelic yeah I totally love the pattern
some kind of animal spirit I don't know I love that the cutout looks so good and it fits so good
and I just love it I think it looks really good so there's a back zip by the way and the next
Is it a back zip or is it a front zip?
I think it's a front zip again.
So the next catsuit is going to be this one.
Not as colorful as the two catsuits before, but slightly creepy is this one.
It's giving a broken doll, Frankenstein, monster, whatever, with all the stitches.
and I also love the lines here because it does make like contouring again and nice
butt shape for example boobie shape we have waist going on here and there is a heart
and we have a belly button here which is also kind of nice of course since it's a front zipper
I can open the zipper again I think I prefer them with an open zipper because
a it's more comfortable because not as tight here and b i can show the girls
but yeah it's a nice look i love the contrast between red white and the black stuff my gothic
heart is in love with this one and also my tim burton heart is liking this one and this one as
well and this is going to be the next one did you see corpse bride because i think this one is giving
Emily vibes paired with Harley Queen and like I don't know General Tim Burton
horror circus stuff but I think it's really cool I kind of dig it I think I
would need pigtails for this suit to do like a Harley Queen look with it yeah
But I like the color combination of blue and purple and of course the blue with my hair.
It's great!
Again, they're just super comfortable.
I love wearing them.
Devil Walking does not only have catsuits but also a huge collection of rave outfits,
two-piece sets and you should definitely check it out.
They have a men's selection.
So every time someone is asking me what can men wear, I'm going to answer the Devil Walking
outfits.
They have couple outfits like for partners.
And yeah, just check out the homepage in the description text.
I have a discount code.
I will put it down there as well.
And I hope you liked this video.
I think the favorite of mine was the first, the nun.
But also the pink one, actually.
Just make one.
Anyway, I hope you enjoyed it.
Leave a comment, leave a thumbs up.
and check out my Patreon. I hope to see you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye.